export default [
    {
        question: 'What is the capitol of California',
        choices: ['Sacremento', 'Austin', 'Seattle', 'Washington DC'],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the capitol of the USA',
        choices: ['Sacremento', 'Austin', 'Seattle', 'Washington DC'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'In which ocean is the island nation of Mauritius?',
        choices: ['Pacific', 'Atlantic', 'Artic', 'Indian'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'On what continent is Saudi Arabia located?',
        choices: ['Africa', 'Asia', 'North America', 'Europe'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which state in the USA is a cluster of islands?',
        choices: ['Alaska', 'Hawaii', 'Guam', 'Midway'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the capitol of Sweden?',
        choices: ['Sacremento', 'Austin', 'Stockholm', 'Gothenburg'],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the capitol of Spain?',
        choices: ['Berlin', 'Madrid', 'Barcelona', 'Nice'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the capitol of Norway',
        choices: ['Stockholm', 'Madrid', 'Seattle', 'Oslo'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the capitol of New York',
        choices: ['NYC', 'Albany', 'Rockfeld', 'Richmond'],
        answer: 1
    }
    // {
    //     question: 'What is used to style webpages',
    //     choices: ['Python', 'CSS', 'HTML', 'Javascript'],
    //     answer: 1
    // }

];
